‪FEBUREZE, 99% ODOR REMOVAL
‪TASTY RICE CRACKERS
‪Deodorizing spray?
‪Um, Yamada…
‪Do I…
‪Um… Uh… So…
‪Sorry. Never mind.
‪With the bag, that comes to 1, 563 yen.
‪Okay.
‪This isn't really something you ask
‪someone while they're on their shift…
‪Here is your change.
‪Thank you, and have a nice day.
‪Thanks.
‪Toxic workplace.
‪Toxic boss.
‪Deodorizing products.
‪Something he wanted to ask.
‪Could it be…
‪Sasaki.
‪Were you accused
‪of smelling like cigarettes?
‪Tayama, are you psychic or something?
‪You must think everyone
‪around you is psychic.
‪I saw you buying deodorizing spray
‪while out on the sales floor.
‪Wha… When did you see me?
‪Well, it's not a lie…
‪Yeah. You got it.
‪The boss is a militant nonsmoker,
‪and he yelled at me to "Fix that smell."
‪Damn, I'm good.
‪Well, that's a smoker's lot in life.
‪Brush your teeth after you smoke.
‪That should get rid of the smell.
‪Then all that's left to do
‪is to just spray down your clothes.
‪But even then…
‪some people might still complain,
‪like they did for me--
‪Tayama, you're amazing!
‪That's so cool
‪that you know all this stuff!
‪Not really.
‪Just a few tips I picked up from a senior.
‪And now you're the one to teach me.
‪Sasaki. Shake.
‪Huh? Oh, sure.
‪Hey, wait. "Shake"?
‪Tayama?
‪This is for you.
‪It's a deodorizing mist that I use.
‪Whoa… It looks expensive. Are you sure?
‪It's used, and I have more at home.
‪Just take it.
‪Thank you.
‪I'm going to feel very stylish.
‪It's mild enough
‪that you can use it regularly
‪without bothering your workmates.
‪Wow, so it's scented?
‪What does it smell like?
‪Wanna check?
‪I sprayed some around here, so go ahead.
‪I'm not going to sniff you!
‪I thought you'd take the bait
‪and go in for a sniff.
‪Tayama, do you think
‪I'm a dog or something?
‪A Labrador retriever, maybe?
‪Huh? A Labra-what?
‪-It's a dog.
‪-You really do think I'm a dog!
‪HAPPY CORP.
‪COMPANY MOTTO
‪"NEVER REST…"
‪Now, just to spray myself with this…
‪Actually, how much should I be putting on?
‪I tend to just do a quick spritz
‪with the deodorizing spray.
‪You sure do take
‪your public image to heart.
‪Suzuki!
‪Telling smokers they stink is just
‪the manager's version of "good morning."
‪You take everything too literally.
‪Yes, but!
‪Apparently if you brush your teeth after
‪smoking and spritz some deodorizing mist…
‪Voilà! Instant odor control.
‪Or so I've been told.
‪You've been told? By whom?
‪Well, uh…
‪TAYAMA - STORE CLERK
‪WE SMOKE TOGETHER
‪Go on. Introduce me.
‪That's cold! Why the hell would you--
‪Wow, that does smell good!
‪I'll bet the wife will fall head
‪over heels for you smelling this good.
‪You magnificent fool…
‪Keiko is already head over heels for me.
‪But, hey, there's no harm
‪in raising the bar. Am I right?
‪Tell me more.
‪It's like I said. You just brush
‪your teeth and spray some mist.
‪Just a little spritz, like this…
‪SUPER S
‪OPEN 24 HOURS
‪Hello, and welcome!
‪Here is your change.
‪Thank you.
‪Oh?
‪Sasaki, something's different today.
‪You kind of smell like Tayama.
‪Wait, I…
‪I'm so embarrassed!
‪She gave me a mist spray the other day.
‪But I never found out
‪how much you're supposed to spray.
‪Guess I sprayed a little too much.
‪Sorry! Thank you very much!
‪Yamada, you're good to go now.
‪-Are you okay? Is something wrong?
‪-Oh…
‪I went to tease someone, but…
‪But it actually backfired on me.
‪It's nice, isn't it?
‪RESTROOM
‪ELEVATOR
‪All hail Master Tayama.
‪ETIQUETTE MASTER
‪I hope she likes my token of thanks.
‪Tayama, good eve…
‪Another employee?
‪And you are?
‪My name is Sasaki.
‪Well, well. Sasaki, is it?
‪You seem like a suspicious chap.
‪I'm calling the cops.
‪No, please! Wait!
‪I'm an acquaintance of Tayama!
‪I was wandering around,
‪looking for a place to smoke,
‪when Tayama was kind enough
‪to invite me over.
‪And so I've just been going
‪along with her offer ever since.
‪Who's "Tayama"?
‪And actually, I know this chap…
‪This is the guy who's always lining up and
‪smiling like a goose at Yamada's register.
‪MY DOG BETH
‪I remember, because he looks
‪just like the family dog back home.
‪But who is "Tayama"?
‪Don't you mean Yamada?
‪Why do you bring Yamada into this?
‪I mean Tayama.
‪She's a young lady, mature for her age,
‪and she wears a cool jacket.
‪She said she's friends with Yamada.
‪Oh. This chap's getting played.
‪So you're here for another smoke
‪with Yama… Yama…
‪I mean, "Tayama" tonight?
‪Oh, no. I just came to give her something.
‪Something?
‪Has she got you as her sugar daddy?
‪It's a thank-you gift!
‪A thank-you gift?
‪Tayama should be out soon.
‪Want me to go get her?
‪Oh, no. You don't have to do that.
‪I was only going to give it to her
‪if she just happened to be around.
‪I'm sorry to trouble you, but could you
‪perhaps give it to her instead?
‪She'll know what it's for.
‪Sorry to bother you on your break.
‪He really does look like the family dog.
‪Beth!
‪Goto.
‪Where was my invitation
‪for this little smoke break?
‪Yamada. I've got a bone to pick with you.
‪Huh? What'd I do?
‪You've been out here smoking
‪with customers, haven't you?
‪I wasn't smoking.
‪You're a liar, Yamada!
‪Don't even try to deny it.
‪I already heard about it
‪from a Mr. Sasaki.
‪Was he here?
‪He just left.
‪Unbelievable. I almost
‪reported him for suspicious activity.
‪He said to give this to "Tayama."
‪Something about it being a thank-you gift.
‪That's you, right? "Tayama."
‪And talk about lazy.
‪"Tayama" and "Yamada"?
‪I'll bet he's the only chap
‪to fall for that.
‪You shouldn't be messing around so much
‪with a nice old chap like him.
‪Hey, are you even listening--
‪I told him it was nothing.
‪Oh, I see what this is.
‪GOTO'S STORE MANAGER METER
‪SENSE FOR ROMANCE VS. MORALITY
‪This is just the sort of entertainment
‪you want on a boring night shift…
‪I'll let 'em be for a while.
‪I left in such a hurry.
‪I hope Tayama didn't get in trouble.
‪Don't go bringing in strays!
‪I'm sorry for bringing him.
‪I'm confiscating your present!
‪You're too cruel…
‪No more smoking for you!
‪Have you no mercy?
‪I'D LOVE FOR YOU
‪TO SLICE MY WATERMELON EVERY DAY
‪Who'd have thought the melon plot
‪would rear its head up again?
‪I can't wait for the next volume.
‪Which one do I read next?
‪LIBRARY
‪THE CATCHER IN THE MELON PATCH
‪Oh. It's you, Yamada.
‪Hello.
‪I thought you were
‪only on the night shift today?
‪Chief Maezawa was struggling
‪to put the schedule together,
‪so here I am anyway.
‪And you're logging your hours properly?
‪Yep. All done and dusted.
‪Good girl.
‪Hey, Goto.
‪You really have given up
‪on paper cigarettes, haven't you?
‪Yeah.
‪This is way more socially acceptable.
‪And I got sick of spritzing myself down
‪and brushing my teeth after.
‪Says the one who taught me all that.
‪Well? There's no point
‪beating around the bush.
‪If you've got something to say,
‪just spit it out.
‪YAMA-GULP
‪It's just… I never did ask whether
‪it was okay to keep smoking out back.
‪Huh? Oh.
‪You mean with that old chap?
‪You didn't not report him so you could
‪"dispose" of him in your own way, right?
‪You didn't bury him
‪out back somewhere, did you?
‪Where do you want the bullet hole? Well?
‪Anywhere but the lungs!
‪Why would I do that?
‪It may have been in one ear
‪and out the other for you,
‪but all I said was
‪you shouldn't mess with him "so much."
‪"So much." Meaning do it in moderation.
‪I'm letting it slide because it's on your
‪own time and it's not holding up the team.
‪But if you do go beyond what I consider
‪"in moderation, " I'll put a stop to it.
‪Otherwise, you're fine.
‪End of story.
‪Lucky me!
‪Hey, Yamada!
‪You tell me if anything happens, y'hear?
‪Sure, but… What's going to happen?
‪Isn't it obvious?
‪You tell me if your heart
‪starts leaping for joy.
‪Okay. See you later.
‪I really ought to give her
‪a proper apology.
‪And all I wanted was to thank her.
‪Who do I think I am, causing her trouble?
‪You're suspicious.
‪Forgive me!
‪Tayama?
‪What are you doing, being all sneaky like?
‪I ran into another employee
‪here the other day.
‪You didn't get in trouble, did you?
‪Oh. You met the store manager.
‪Store manager?
‪It wasn't a big deal.
‪And more importantly, come here.
‪Hey, wait--
‪You mean the store manager
‪said it was okay to smoke here?
‪She said it was fine in moderation.
‪"In moderation…"
‪That doesn't sound
‪like an actual go-ahead…
‪Oh, and Sasaki?
‪This thing.
‪It's cute.
‪You said you didn't want any money,
‪but I still wanted to thank you.
‪I'm glad you like it.
‪Yeah.
‪Just looking at this thing makes me smile.
‪Oh, really?
‪I imagine you
‪pondering over what to buy for me.
‪Why does that make you smile?
‪Well, you must have had
‪a tough time finding this, right?
‪It's not easy to find something
‪as cute as this in stores these days.
‪So when I think about you asking
‪the store staff where they sell them,
‪and going to the knickknack section
‪that's always full of women,
‪feeling awkward, but pushing through it
‪to find something for me anyway…
‪Tayama,
‪you really are psychic, aren't you?
‪Well, just picturing it all
‪makes me smile.
‪I think you're just trying
‪to poke fun at an old man.
‪Oh? I wouldn't say that.
‪You make me feel better.
‪I can't tell if she's joking
‪or being serious.
‪Thank you.
‪I'll guard this with my life.
‪I guess I don't mind either way.
‪Hey, Sasaki.
‪Isn't it about time
‪you ash your cigarette?
‪You're right.
‪You can use this.
‪How good is it
‪that you get to use it right away?
‪Thank yo--
‪Isn't that a little close?
‪You need to ash it properly,
‪or else you'll burn yourself.
‪Go on then.
‪Ash it.
‪No…
‪You could just hand it to me.
‪Then go on and take it.
‪What…
‪A little more.
‪More!
‪Tayama.
‪Why are you moving it away from me?
‪I am, aren't I?
‪You sure do have long arms, don't you?
‪Come on, Tayama.
‪My arm is gonna…
‪Pain relief patches?
‪Don't tell me…
‪Are you okay?
‪I'm fine!
‪Sorry, I just choked on air
‪for a second there.
‪I really am sorry. Please forgive me.
‪Yamada, there's no need
‪for such a big apology.
‪I guess older dudes really do spend
‪more time recovering from a pulled muscle.
‪Sasaki, please forgive me…
‪It's fine. Everything's fine, Yamada!
‪-Please forgive me.
‪-Please, stop!
‪-Please stop apologizing.
‪-I am so terribly sorry.
‪I'm telling you. It's fine!
‪Subtitle translation by: Rychelle Brittain